漫威影业出品
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
好了
There.
■
翻译：夜魔奶
到底了
It just hit.
至少有四十层楼
It's gotta be 40 stories, at least.
翻译：夜魔奶
趴下
Down!
校对：夜魔奶
他们到处都是  起码有六个人
They're on all sides. Half a dozen, at least.
时间轴：夜魔寿司
-我遇到麻烦了  -有我呢
- I got a problem. - Right with you.
不  你不明白  我没法感受到那些人
No, you don't get it. I can't get a read on these guys.
后期：聪炒吉丁  8T     总监：夜魔奶
没有声音  没有心跳  什么都没有
There's no sound, there's no heartbeat, there's nothing.
-他们专门训练隐藏自己  -你怎么知道
- They're trained to hide themselves. - How do you know?
别管那些人  把注意力集中在武器上
Don't focus on the fighters, track their weapons.
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
-他们有剑  -他们有剑  我听得到
- They have swords. - They have swords, I can hear.
艾丽卡  不
Elektra, no!
马修...
Matthew...
那么...
So...
谁想离开这里呢
who wants to get the hell out of here?
夜
魔
侠
第二季  第八集
她失血太多
She's losing too much blood.
伤太重
Hell of a scrape.
你要带她去哪儿
Where are you taking her?
他们还在追  速度真快
They're still coming. Fast little shits.
-他们是谁  棍叟  -现在不是聊天的时候
- Who are they, Stick? - Bad time to chat.
-马特  -交给我
- Matty! - On it!
-小心点  -好的
- Watch your ass. - Yeah.
不不不  她快不行了
No, no, no. No, she's dying.
-棍叟  她要死了  -我能救她
- Stick, she's dying. - Not if I can stop it.
我们得送她去医院
We need to get her to a hospital.
医生帮不了她  我能
Doctors can't help her. I can.
我们去你那儿  这是她唯一的机会
We're going to your place. It's her only shot.
亲爱的  坚持住  坚持住
Sweetie, stay with me. Stay with me.
第二波来了  把她扶稳了
Second wave. Brace her.
这一波完蛋了
End of that batch.
还有更多人
There'll be more.
永远有更多人
Always more.
我不瞒你  情况不妙
I'm not gonna lie to you. This is bad.
她怎么了
What's happening to her?
你有小苏打吗
You got baking soda?
冰箱里有  怎么了
Yeah, in the fridge, why?
用来中和马桶清洁剂里的酸
To neutralize the acid in the toilet bowl cleaner.
还需要威士忌  镊子  红茶
Plus whiskey, pliers, black tea.
告诉我怎么回事  棍叟
Tell me what's going on, Stick.
你想继续聊天还是救你的女朋友
Do you wanna talk or save your girlfriend?
她的心跳加速
Her heart's skipping.
威士忌
Whiskey.
她血液中的毒素让她身体所有机能瘫痪了
The toxins in her bloodstream are shutting everything down.
她能活下来吗
Is she gonna live?
小苏打
Baking soda?
我以为你能行的
I thought you got it.
马修
Matthew!
我需要镊子和热茶
I need pliers and hot tea.
镊子就在你背后
The pliers are behind you.
马修
Matthew...
我在呢  我在呢
I'm here. I'm here.
如果我死了...
If I die...
不  你不会死的  听到了吗
No, you're not gonna die. You hear me?
艾丽卡  看着我
Elektra, look at me.
看着我
Hey, hey, focus on me.
呼气  呼气
Breathe. Breathe.
很好  很好
That's good. That's good.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉我没告诉你
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
把她搬过来
Bring her in here!
好吧
Yeah.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
-干净的毯子  -好的
- Clean sheets. - Yeah.
你能救她吗
Can you save her?
她得先受点苦
Not before I make her worse.
天啊  棍叟  轻点
Oh, Jesus! Stick, take it easy!
这些刀刃上有毒
Those blades were poisoned.
如果我不赶紧
She'll be dead in 20 minutes
给她处理伤口  她过个二十分钟就没命了
if I don't pull some serious juju out of my ass.
赶紧去烧茶
Make the goddamn tea!
放松
Easy.
放松  放松  姑娘  我在这呢
Easy. Easy, young lady. I'm right here.
宽恕那些冒犯我们的人
...forgive those who trespass against us.
马特  利用你的听力
Matty, use that hearing of yours.
她的心跳如何
How's her heart rate?
很好  稳定下来了
Yeah. Yeah, it's good. It's steady.
毯子
Sheets.
处理不算特别干净...
Not too neat...
但是...
but...
这样也可以
it'll do.
茶呢
Tea?
谢谢
Thank you.
她会恢复吗
She'll recover?
过二十四小时就知道了
Twenty-four hours will tell.
我知道她挺过去过更严重的伤
I've known her to pull through worse.
你刚说什么
What'd you just say?
艾丽一直是一个真正的斗士
Ellie's a real fighter. Always has been.
你...你认识她吗
You... you know her?
我没跟你提起过吗
I didn't mention that?
怎么回事  你怎么会认识艾丽卡
What the hell's going on? How do you know Elektra?
-我还没处理好呢  -我要知道答案
- I'm not done in there. - I want some answers!
每个人都想要点什么
Everybody wants something.
你想要我把你扔出去吗
Do you want me to throw you out?
除非你想让她死
Not unless you want her to die.
坐下  马特
Sit down, Matty.
他在哪儿
Where is he?
我可能之前跟他说今天待在家里吧
Um, I may have told him just to stay home today.
什么
You what?
他根本就不该这么做
He wasn't actually supposed to do it.
福吉  昨天到底发生了什么
Whoa, whoa, Foggy, what the hell happened yesterday?
我一个人做不到
I can't do this alone.
我甚至根本不想接这个案子
I didn't even wanna take this case.
-没事的  -整个城市都在看着
- It'll be okay, I-- - The whole city is watching.
如果搞砸了  我以后就没活了
If I screw up, I'd never work again.
老实说  你以后可能也别想找到工作了
And, frankly, you'd probably never work again,
-你也牵扯进来...  -别说了  福吉
- either, by association, which-- - Stop, Foggy.
别想着搞砸后怎么办  败诉后怎么办
Stop thinking about screwing up, about losing.
你得想想胜诉
You need to think about winning.
雷·斯库诺弗上校  美国海军陆战队
Colonel Ray Schoonover, United States Marine Corps.
你向上帝发誓
Do you swear to tell the truth,
只会说出真相  知无不言吗
the whole truth and nothing but the truth, so help you God?
我发誓
I do.
你可以的
You got this.
律师
Counsel?
上校  你认识被告多久了
Colonel, how long have you known the defendant?
要我说不到十年了
I'd say, the better part of a decade.
他在海军陆战队服役期间跟我认识的
Most of his career in the Marine Corps.
那你应该知道他在中东服役的事吧
So you're familiar with his service in the Middle East?
阿富汗  巴基斯坦  伊朗
Afghanistan, Pakistan, Iran?
是的  非常了解
Yes, very familiar.
你能否告诉我们
I wonder if you could tell us
弗兰克·卡塞尔上尉如何赢得海军奖章的
how Lieutenant Frank Castle won the Navy Cross?
那次任务性质特殊  你应理解
Due to the nature of that mission, you'll have to understand that
具体情况属于国家机密
the precise circumstances are classified.
那不是机密的部分呢
How about the part that's not?
弗兰克·卡塞尔上尉隶属其中一个小队
Lieutenant Frank Castle was part of a small team.
他负责去兴都库什山脉附近
He was conducting a close target reconnaissance
接近目标进行侦查
in the vicinity of the Hindu Kush.
任务遭到了破坏
The mission became compromised,
他们三面遭到敌人攻击
taking enemy contact on three sides.
卡塞尔上尉想中止任务
Lieutenant Castle wanted to abort.
他说这任务会失败  及时中止才能挽救更多性命
Said the mission was a bust, pulling the plug would save lives.
-负责的军官说不行  -为什么
- Officer in charge said "No." - And why was that?
也许他想在胸前多挂一枚奖章
Maybe he wanted more medals on his chest.
这不重要  不管怎么说  弗兰克是对的
Doesn't matter. Either way, Frank was right.
他们被切断后路  困在山谷里
They were cut off, boxed into a canyon.
然后发生了什么
And what happened next?
头一个小时  负责该行动的军官
Within the first hour, the officer in charge of that mission
就被炸飞了胳膊
got his arm blown off.
所以卡塞尔中尉接替指挥
So Lieutenant Castle assumed command.
他唯一的目标就是带着他的人活着逃出去
His only goal was to get his men out alive.
敌方在我们
The enemy had set up an ambush
唯一能够停靠飞机的LZ附近安排了埋伏
at the only LZ that would accommodate one of our birds.
什么意思  上校
Sorry, Colonel?
LZ是指能够停靠直升飞机的降落区
LZ is a landing zone that can accommodate a helicopter.
敌方占据了降落区
So the enemy, they block this landing zone,
他们知道这是这支小队唯一能存活的机会
knowing it was the only shot the team had to get out alive.
他们只要等在那里
All they had to do was wait.
他们知道弗兰克的小队肯定会去那里
They knew that Frank's team had to come to them.
瓮中之鳖
Fish in a barrel.
可以这么说
So to speak.
但是鱼不知道自己命不久矣
only fish don't know they're gonna die.
他们都知道
These men did.
弗兰克一个人
Frank went to the LZ
前往降落区  把这些混蛋引走
all by himself to draw the bastards away.
他为什么不派他的手下这样做呢
Why didn't he order one of his men to do it?
他当然可以派
He certainly could have.
但这不是他的风格
Not his style.
他们只能听到枪声大作  好像天都塌下来了
So the men hear the fire fight break out. All hell breaks loose.
弗兰克一个人对不知道多少人
Frank against God knows how many.
然后一片寂静
And then there was silence.
他们想"完了  弗兰克死了  轮到我们了"
The team thinks, "That's it. Frank's dead, and we're next."
然后他们就听到机浆声  直升机到了
Next sound they hear is the helos, the helicopters.
他们赶到降落区  你知道他们看到了什么吗
They get to the landing zone, you know what they see?
弗兰克·卡塞尔  站在那儿对他们笑
Frank Castle, standing there, grinning.
他周围躺着23个圣战分子  全死了
Thirty-two muj surrounding him, all dead.
这家伙一个人干掉了整个降落区的人
Son of a gun cleared that entire LZ all by himself.
怎么做到的
How?
因为他是弗兰克·卡塞尔
By being Frank Castle.
-他的人都活下来了吗  -全活下来了
- And his men survived? - All of 'em.
包括那个一开始
Including the idiot officer
让他们陷入困境的蠢军官
that got 'em trapped in the first place.
你会如何评价弗兰克·卡塞尔
If you had to sum up Frank Castle, how would you do it?
我会说弗兰克·卡塞尔
I would say Frank Castle is a man
是一个愿意用自己的性命保护他人的人
who would gladly give his life to keep others safe.
那对于他今日被控的这些罪行呢
And the crimes he's accused of today?
你认识的他会犯下这些罪吗
Could the man you knew have committed them?
绝对不会
Absolutely not.
我认识的弗兰克·卡塞尔上尉是一个英雄
Lieutenant Frank Castle that I know is a hero.
他值得我们的尊重...
A man who deserves our respect...
和感激
and our gratitude.
他们不是一个人
Not the same man.
谢谢你  先生  没有问题了  法官大人
Thank you, sir. No more questions, Your Honor.
公诉方
People?
我想亲自谢谢你
I'd like to personally thank you
为这个国家做出的贡献  上校
for your service to this country, Colonel.
我父亲曾在越南服役
My father served in Vietnam.
你知道他怎么跟我描述奖章的吗
Do you know what he told me about medals?
不知道  女士
No, ma'am.
他说唯一知道发生了什么的人
He said the only people who truly know what happened
是当时在场的人
are the ones that were there.
你讲的故事很棒  上校...
You told a nice story, Colonel...
但是我们怎么知道事实正如你所描述的呢
but how can we know that it happened the way you described?
也许我没有说清楚  我在场  女士
Well, perhaps I wasn't clear. I was there, ma'am.
没有听弗兰克的话  让他的人陷入困境的军官...
That officer that didn't listen to Frank, got his men trapped...
就在你面前
you're looking at him.
你要相信我
And believe me when I tell you,
我每天都在感谢上帝只让我丢了一只手
I thank God every day that I only lost my arm.
他救了我的命  整个小队的命
That man saved my life, the lives of his entire team.
如果我的话管用
If it was up to me,
绝对会给他挂上一枚荣誉勋章
he'd have a Medal of Honor hanging around his neck.
没有更多问题了  法官大人
No further questions at this time, Your Honor.
你怎么会在他的资料中漏了这一点
How'd you miss that in his file?
所有名字都被改过了
All the names were redacted.
不大妙
Not good.
这还用说
No shit.
换做是马特也不会做得比你更好
Hey, Matt couldn't have done it better.
太厉害了
It was good.
她怎么样了
How is she?
她会活下来的
Well... she'll live.
是吗  你确定吗
Yeah? You sure?
像我对其他事一样确定
Sure as I am of anything.
天啊  我们不是早就来过这一套了吗
Jesus, didn't we do this already?
说吧  棍叟
Start talking, Stick.
都是跟战争有关
It's about the war.
什么
What is?
所有的一切
All of it.
罗克森  中城圈  那个洞  艾丽卡
Roxxon, Midland Circle, the damn hole, Elektra--
从我遇到你开始
All right, you've been using
你就用这个战争作为借口
this war as an excuse since the day I met you,
但是你还是什么都没有告诉我
and you still haven't told me a goddamn thing about it.
-你知道我怎么想的吗  -告诉我
- You know what I think? - Tell me.
我觉得你满口胡言
I think you're full of shit.
我觉得根本没有什么战争
I don't think there is any war.
我觉得你就是个想揍人的老打手
I think you're just a sick old fighter dying to hit people,
所以你就编故事  给你的所作所为找理由
so you make up stories to justify your behavior.
然后  你说服那些伤者...
And then, you rope in the wounded...
这样你就能坐看他们以命相搏
so that you can sit back and watch them throw away their lives,
让你感觉自己很重要
and you can feel important.
坐下
Sit down.
坐下  马特
Sit down, Matty.
一切要从几个世纪前说起
It all began centuries ago.
谁也不知道多久以前
Nobody knows how many,
但是我们要插手的事...
but the shit we're dipping into...
年代非常久远
is ancient.
那时候
Back then,
军阀和他们的团伙统治了一切
warlords and their gangs ruled the countryside.
和现在没什么不同
Not that much different from today.
人们嗜血  贪婪地瓜分战利品
Bloodthirsty, greedy brutes after loot,
女人  美酒之类的东西
pussy, booze, same ol', same ol'.
但是  有一天
But... one day,
那帮混蛋中  有一个家伙
one of these collections of assholes
发现了一件其他人都无法理解的东西
comes across a thing they can barely understand.
真正的宝物
Real treasure.
不是金子  宝石之类的东西
Not gold, or rubies, or any of that.
他们发现了秘密
They found the secret.
什么秘密
What secret?
永生
Immortality.
让死者复生
Bringing the dead back to life.
得了吧  棍叟
Come on, Stick.
你不是天主教徒吗  马特
I thought you were a Catholic, Matty.
你的信仰不就建立在
Doesn't your whole belief system
一个这样做过的家伙身上吗
hinge on one guy pulling that off?
所以...
So...
摒弃了对死亡的恐惧
Free from the fear of death,
这些混蛋站了出来
these pieces of shit step up,
杀掉了他们的主人  掌管了一切
kill their master, take over,
让整个远东都被
and paint the shores of the Far East
阻拦他们者的鲜血所染红
with the blood of anybody who stands in their way.
他们的人数  权力和财富日益增长...
They grow in size, power, wealth...
扩散到整个亚洲
spread across Asia...
他们给自己起了一个名号
and finally give themselves a name.
山手
Yaminote.
意思是"手和会"
It means, "The Hand."
他们有什么目的吗
And did they have a goal?
武器  永远是为了武器
Weapons. It's always weapons.
枪和炸弹之类的吗
Like, guns, bombs?
不止
Worse.
一个叫黑空的东西
Thing called a Black Sky.
这个黑空有什么用
So, what's it do, this, uh, Black Sky?
没人知道
Nobody knows exactly.
为什么
Why not?
因为他们从来没有唤醒过
Because they've never activated one.
他们试过了  他们会继续尝试
They've tried. They'll try again.
但是...
But...
手和会犯了一个错误
the Hand made one mistake.
他们树敌
They made enemies.
没错
Bingo.
有人说只是一个孩子
Some say it was just a kid.
手和会侵入他的村庄  杀了所有人
Hand comes into his village, kills everyone...
几乎所有人
almost.
这孩子...
Kid...
从他死去的母亲胸口拔出刀子...
pulls the knife from the breast of his dead mother...
开始复仇
and goes to work.
他击败了不少手和会的精锐战士
He cuts down some of the Hand's finest warriors.
他们死了...那孩子活了下来
They're lying dead... kid's standing.
他们称他为真纯会
They give him a name. The Chaste.
他只是一个孩子  一个人吗
And he's just one kid? Alone?
这孩子长大后  招揽了很多战士
Kid grows up, rounds up every warrior he can.
有男有女  有老有少  只要能打就行
Men, women, young, old, doesn't matter as long as they kick ass.
他们的确很能打
And they do.
毫不留情
Without mercy.
唯一能够保护全世界不被手和会吞噬的组织
And the only protection this world has against the Hand.
在这个故事里...
Now, in this fairy tale...
你是真纯会吧  那...
you're the Chaste, right? That's...
是吗
Is that it?
所以我才没告诉你
It's why I didn't tell you.
不不  没...没关系  这让你非常重要
No, no, it's... It's good. It leaves you front and center.
找到手和会  压制住黑空
Finding the Hand, keeping the Black Skies at bay.
心情好就杀人
Murdering when it suits you.
信不信随你
Believe it or don't.
事实上  你发誓要保护这这座城市
The fact remains that the city you're sworn to protect
不知不觉中已经成为了战争的起点
is ground zero in a war it doesn't even know is happening.
那个洞只是一个开端
That hole is just the start.
你可以杀人  可以去死
So, you can kill, die,
也可以坐看地狱厨房燃烧殆尽
or sit on your ass and watch Hell's Kitchen burn...
但这场战争比你  或我
but this war is bigger than you,
或我们任何人的问题...
or me, or any of our...
都要重要
problems.
你把艾丽卡拉到了你这边  对吗
And you've pulled Elektra to your side, haven't you?
欢迎来到这个世界  孩子
Welcome to the world, kid.
艾丽卡为我效命
Elektra works for me.
子弹从右下方穿过了
The bullet penetrated Mr. Castle's skull
卡塞尔先生的头骨
in the lower right quadrant,
更准确地来说  是蝶额缝线
or more specifically, the sphenofrontal suture,
也就是蝶骨
which is the cranial suture
与额骨之间的颅缝
between the sphenoid bone and the frontal bones,
分别是这里和这里
both here and here.
我相信我的专家证人想说的是
I believe what my expert witness is trying to convey
我的当事人  弗兰克·卡塞尔的伤...
is that my client, Frank Castle, was shot...
头部中枪  近距离开枪  处决式
point blank, execution style, in the head.
你能描述一下卡塞尔先生
Could you please describe the damage
中弹后所受到的伤害吗
Mr. Castle sustained from the bullet?
头骨因冲击而破碎  对他的
It fragmented on impact, causing damage
右额叶与颞叶都造成了一定伤害
in both the right frontal lobe and temporal lobe of his brain.
这种伤会有什么影响
What are the effects of such an injury?
卡塞尔先生会经历所谓的交感风暴
Mr. Castle is suffering from what we call sympathetic storming.
由于他的交感神经系统过度活跃
It's a heightened and ongoing state of fight or flight,
他会持续处于逃跑或战斗的模式
in which the sympathetic nervous system is hyperactive.
他好像在一遍一遍地重温他所受的创伤
As if he is reliving the incident of trauma over and over again.
这可以使一个比较温和的人变得...
It can plunge a seemingly peaceful individual into...
疯狂  情绪混乱
mental and emotional chaos.
听上去很像创伤后遗症
It sure sounds a lot like PTSD.
不  我们不是这个目的
No, that's not where we're going.
听着吧
Just... listen.
你能为陪审团解释一些吗
Could you define it for the jury, please?
极端情绪障碍
Extreme emotional disturbance.
这是双刃剑
It's twofold.
首先  被告会
First, the defendant is so
因为自己情绪困扰而失控
emotionally disturbed that he loses control.
然后  被告会为自己的困扰
And second, the defendant has a reasonable explanation
从他的角度来看  做出合理的解释
for said disturbance, from his point of view.
你知道弗兰克·卡塞尔头部受伤时
Are you aware that Frank Castle's wife, son, and daughter
他的妻子  儿女
were all murdered right in front of him
都在他面前被杀了吗
when he sustained the brain injury in question?
根据你的说法  这个伤
An injury which, you say,
会让他一直处于精神和情绪不稳定的状态
keeps him in a perpetual state of mental and emotional chaos?
我知道
I am, yes.
既然如此  你认为弗兰克·卡塞尔的精神状态
With that in mind, would you say that Frank Castle's mental state
是否符合"极端情绪障碍"的定义
satisfies the definition of "Extreme emotional disturbance"?
反对  妄下定论
Objection, calls for a conclusion.
法官大人  李博士是脑部问题专家
Your Honor, Dr. Lee is an expert on the brain.
他有资格发表看法
He is qualified to an opinion,
这个看法不仅与本案息息相关
and said opinion is not only relevant,
对本案来说还非常重要
but imperative to the case.
驳回
Overruled.
李博士
Dr. Lee?
在我看来  我认为他处于极端情绪障碍之中
Personally, I do believe he is suffering from EED, yes.
处于极端情绪障碍的人
And one who's suffering from extreme emotional disturbance,
会不会自愿谋划犯罪
is it possible to willfully premeditate a crime?
他的行为都应该归于冲动犯罪
Any infractions would be considered crimes of passion.
你还有多少其他病人
How many of your other patients
目睹自己的家人
witnessed their families
在自己面前被人残酷地杀害
being brutally murdered right in front of them?
除了弗兰克·卡塞尔之外
Other than Frank Castle?
只有他一个人
He's the only one.
那你是否觉得
And so would you say the
弗兰克的精神状态条件
circumstances surrounding Frank's mental state
和你的其他病人都不一样
is different than those of your other patients?
是的
I would.
简单来说  主要有什么区别
And what exactly would that difference be, in simple terms?
弗兰克·卡塞尔经历了地狱
Frank Castle's been through hell.
谢谢
Thank you.
你杀了我爸爸
You killed my dad!
我才不管你经历了什么
I don't give a shit what you've been through!
-肃静  法庭上请肃静  -你杀了他
- Order! Order in the court! - You killed him!
-我看到他在棺材里...  -请把这位年轻人带出去
- I saw him in his coffin... - Please remove that young man now.
他是我爸爸  现在他死了
He was my dad, and now he's gone!
我现在请你们
I'm now instructing each and
每个人都忽视刚刚发生的骚动
every one of you to disregard that outburst
不要影响到你们对于本案的看法
and to not let it influence your opinions on this case.
是我干的
I did that.
对吧
Right?
我杀死了那孩子的父亲  是我做的
That kid, I took his father from him. I did that.
是啊
Yeah, you did.
弗兰克  我不能评判你的行为
Look, Frank, I can't judge you.
对你来说也很难熬吧
That was tough in there for you, right?
很难受吧
It was, um, hard?
是的
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
你要为我做一些事
You gotta do something for me.
我要你出来作证
I need you to take the stand.
为什么呢  我为什么要...
Come on, for what? Why would I...
陪审团需要知道你到底发生了什么
The jury has to know what happened to you,
你每天都经历了些什么
what you go through every single day.
今天下午过后...
After this afternoon...
我觉得我们没有其他机会了
I don't think we have any other shot.
怎么了
What?
你觉得会发生什么事
And what do you think is gonna happen here?
我们赢不了的
We're not gonna win this thing.
没错  但我们可以减少判罚
No, but we can still reduce the charges.
那对你来说可能不重要
Look, that might not be important to you,
但对我来说很重要
but it is important to me.
他们都认为你是一个禽兽
All of them, they all think that you're a monster.
但我知道你不是  你不是
But I know that you're not. You're not!
你确定吗
You sure about that?
如果我查到对我家人下手的家伙
What if I find these men that did that to my family?
如果...
What if...
如果什么都没变呢
What if nothing changes?
如果我就是这种人呢
What if this is just me now?
那你也有资格了解这一点吧
Then don't you deserve to know that, too?
福吉
Foggy!
他愿意  他愿意作证
He'll do it. He'll take the stand.
-你是认真的吗  -是啊
- Are you serious? - Yeah.
听着  除非你有更好的主意  我觉得...
Look, unless you have a better idea, I think--
我们怎么会走到这一步
How did we even get here?
这家伙是个杀人犯
This guy's a murderer.
他杀害别人的父母亲友  你也听到那孩子说的话了
He's killed fathers and brothers. You heard that kid.
我们为什么要帮他
Why are we helping him?
你觉得弗兰克
Do you think that Frank
是一个精神正常的人吗
is completely and totally mentally healthy?
-我觉得他疯透了  -是吗
- I think he's batshit. - Yeah?
所以我们要帮他
Well, then that's why you help him.
让他出庭作证  福吉
Put him on the stand, Foggy.
该死  好吧
Shit. Okay.
-不过有一个要求  -好
- One caveat, though. - Okay.
-我们让马特来问话  -不
- We get Matt to do the questioning. - No.
-必须这样  -不行
- Yes. - No.
你做的很好  你让雷耶斯步步后退
You're doing great, okay? You're making Reyes play defense.
你...你不需要马特也能做到
You... you don't need Matt for this.
-我需要他  凯伦  -你为什么经常这样
- I do, Karen! - Why do you always do this?
明明你能做得到
Why do you put Matt in the driver's seat
为什么非让马特来
when you can do this yourself?
马特和我搭档是有原因的
Matt and I are partners for a reason.
有我更擅长的方面
There's some things that I'm better at,
也有他更擅长的方面
and there's things that he's better at.
这就是他更擅长的方面
This is something that he'll be better at.
他才跟弗兰克待了几秒钟
He's barely spent two seconds with Frank.
我知道  但是那孩子几乎毁了我们
I know, but that kid nearly destroyed us in there.
当下  应该让马特来向弗兰克提问
And at this moment, Matt is the right person to question Frank.
就该是他
He just is.
好吧
Okay.
我去找他
I'll get him.
-抱歉  -我们的相遇
- I'm sorry-- - When we met...
是命运吗
was it fate?
是运气吗
Was it luck?
还是一项任务
Or was I a mission?
任务
Mission.
棍叟训练我很久  就像他训练你一样
Stick trained me a long time, like he trained you.
他不是性情中人  但他希望你回来
He's not a sentimental man, but he wanted you back.
他希望你忘掉法律  你的朋友...
He wanted you to forget about law, your friends...
你的城市
your city.
他认为我能让你分心
He thought I could distract you.
他没错
He was right.
不
No.
因为我做了一件我向他保证不会做的事
Because I did the thing I promised him I'd never do.
我爱上了你  马修
I fell in love with you, Matthew.
如果有必要的话  可以听我的心跳
Listen to my heartbeat, if you must.
你知道这是真的
You know it's true.
棍叟跟我说了一些关于日本秘密组织的事
Stick told me about some secret Japanese organization.
手和会
The Hand.
他们会渗入你的城市  不会停手
They won't stop until they've infiltrated your whole city.
杀死真纯会的每一个人
Killed every last member of the Chaste.
-棍叟  -和你
- Stick-- - You.
我们身处前线
We live on the front lines.
不由我们决定
Like it or not.
但这不代表我们要用棍叟的方式战斗
It doesn't mean we have to fight Stick's way.
他杀死敌人  我们不必如此
He kills his enemies, and we don't have to.
这选择说得倒是轻巧
You make that choice sound so easy.
不  这不轻巧  简直不可能
No, it's not easy. It's impossible.
但这是一个选择
But it's a choice and
是我每天都要做的选择
it's a choice that I remake every single day.
有时甚至每一秒
Every second, sometimes.
你也可以
And you can, too.
马修  我有一些你不了解的地方
Matthew, there are things about me you don't know.
-我不需要了解  -我希望你了解
- I don't need to know. - I want you to.
我不在乎你过去做过什么...
I don't care, whatever you've done in the past...
艾丽卡  不管你作过什么选择  你现在自由了
Elektra, whoever you've chosen to be, you're free now, all right?
你可以杀死洞里的那些人  但你没有
You could have killed those men at the hole, but you didn't.
因为你不是棍叟
Because you're not Stick.
他要是让你有那么一点
And screw him for ever making
认为你可能变成他  去他的吧
you feel like you might be, even for a second.
-他听得到  -我不在乎
- He can hear you. - I don't care.
你受伤时  我以为要失去你时  我...
When you were hurt, when I thought I might lose you, I...
我...
I...
我感觉空荡荡的
I felt hollow.
我没有理由相信你
Now, I have no reason to trust you.
你骗我的次数太多了
You've lied to me more times than I can count.
但是如果你离开棍叟
But if you leave Stick...
和我一起
be with me.
跟我一起加入战争
Fight this war by my side.
用我的方式
My way.
我们的方式
Our way.
你为什么这么好
Why are you so good?
我没有
I'm not.
你有
Yes.
你的内心有一束光
There's a light inside you.
你试图在你上大学时掐灭它
I tried to snuff it out in college.
还好我失败了
I'm so lucky I failed.
有人...有人来了
Someone... someone's here.
有人找你
You got company.
凯伦...
Karen...
我们...
Um, let's, uh...
-我们去别的地方  -不  为什么
- let's go somewhere. - No. Why?
-这样我们能谈谈  -我不想谈
- So we can talk. - I don't want to.
我知道这看上去很疯狂  但其实不是
I know this looks crazy, but it's really not.
这不...这不重要
It doesn't... It doesn't matter.
弗兰克·卡塞尔明天要出庭作证了
Frank Castle's going to take the stand tomorrow.
你的朋友需要你的帮助
And your friend could use your help.
就这样
That's all.
很高兴认识你
Nice meetin' ya.
粉丝俱乐部来了
Fan club's here.
弗兰克要出庭作证的消息肯定不胫而走
Word must have gotten out about Frank testifying.
马特最好赶紧出现
Matt better show.
就算他不来  我们也能行吧
If he doesn't, we'll survive. Right?
凯伦  我对昨天...
Karen, I'm so sorry about--
福吉要跟你说一些事
Uh, Foggy wants to walk through some things with you.
你需要我
Yeah, you wanted me here?
先说清楚
Let's be clear.
找你来不是因为你是更好的律师或更好的人
You're not here because you're a better lawyer or person.
找你来是因为你
You're here because you're
几乎和弗兰克·卡塞尔一样疯狂而已
almost as crazy as Frank Castle, and that's it.
所以你叫我来是为了羞辱我吗
So you called me here to insult me?
我是叫你偶尔发挥一下作用
I called you here to be useful, for a change.
我们需要让弗兰克讲的故事能保住他的命
We need to get Frank to tell his story in a way that keeps him
让他不用进监狱
out of prison and alive.
除你之外没有人听过他的故事
No one's heard that story except for you,
因为你就是你
because you're who you are.
不如让你让我和凯伦
Why don't you put all that torture
所受的折磨派上点用场
you put me and Karen through to good use?
现在是时候了
Now would be the time.
律师们  准备好了吗
Counsel, we about ready?
再等一分钟  法官大人
Uh, one more moment, Your Honor.
你看过斯库诺弗和李的庭审记录了吗
Did you read the notes from Schoonover and Lee?
看过了
Yeah.
计划是这样的
Okay, here's the play.
让弗兰克讲一遍他的故事
Walk Frank through his story.
把上校和脑科学家的话联系起来
Connect the dots between the Colonel and the neurologist.
我们不需要证实弗兰克所说的话是真的
We don't have to prove that Frank's version of events is true.
我们只需要让陪审团相信他深信不疑
We just have to convince the jury that he believes it,
每天都在重温
and he relives it every day.
我们就能把这家伙关进疯人院  他属于那里
We can put this guy in the loony bin, where he belongs.
-律师  -是
- Counsel? - Yeah.
法官大人  辩方
Uh, Your Honor, the Defense
请求召弗兰克·卡塞尔出庭作证
would like to call Frank Castle to the stand.
法警  带被告进来
Bailiff, bring in the defendant, please.
告诉我发生了什么
Tell me what's going on.
弗兰克穿着西装
Frank's wearing a suit.
他看上去比我都帅
He looks better than I ever have,
他甚至都没戴领带
and he's not even wearing a tie.
肃静
Order.
想想你要什么  弗兰克
Think about what you want, Frank.
-有点不对劲  -没有回头路了
- Something's not right. - No turning back now.
你愿意向上帝发誓
Do you solemnly swear that you will tell the truth,
你所说的句句属实
the whole truth, and nothing but the truth,
绝无虚言吗
so help you God?
我愿意
Yeah.
请说出你的名字
Please state your name for the record.
弗兰克·卡塞尔
Frank Castle.
卡塞尔先生  你被控犯有多起谋杀重罪
Mr. Castle, you've been charged with multiple capital crimes.
被称作毫无怜悯与悔恨之心的杀手
Been called a killer incapable of empathy or remorse.
是的
Yeah.
我听说是这样
So I hear.
弗兰克...
Frank...
我能叫你弗兰克吗
May I call you Frank?
可以
Yeah.
弗兰克  我们听了很多神经化学
Frank, we've heard a lot about neuro-chemistry...
和心理学上的说法  从科学上
and psychology, and all things unfolding,
展示了你大脑内发生的事
scientifically and otherwise, inside your brain.
但是我只想问你一个问题
But I just have one question I want to ask.
那天发生了什么
What happened that day?
你的家人惨死的那一天
The day your family was so tragically killed.
没事的  弗兰克
It's okay, Frank.
-我知道这很难  -是吗
- I understand, it's difficult. - Do you?
你知道吗
Do you understand?
因为我觉得你什么都不知道
'Cause I don't think you understand shit.
我希望将证人列为敌对证人  法官大人
I'd like permission to treat the witness as hostile, Your Honor?
动议批准
Granted.
好吧  弗兰克
All right, Frank.
你不想告诉我们  那我告诉你
You don't want to tell us? I'll tell you.
我来告诉你你到底是怎样的人
I'm gonna tell you exactly what kind of man you are.
你就是这座城市需要的人
You're the kind of man this city needs.
因为  陪审团的女士们先生们
Because, ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
我们都知道这座城市需要帮助
we all know this city needs help.
现在就需要
Needs it now.
不是明天  不是下周  不是等到了那一天
Not tomorrow, not next week, not when the day comes,
不是等威尔逊·菲斯克的腐败
when the corruption that Wilson Fisk
被全面清除
left in his wake is flushed out for good,
警方终于开始干实事的一天
and the police force is finally back on its feet.
我们现在就需要
We need it now.
因为这座城市病了
'Cause this city's been sick.
单靠警察没法补救  他们需要...
And the cops, they can't fix it alone, they need...
我们都需要那些
We all need men and women
愿意站出来战斗的人
who are willing to take the fight themselves.
那些愿意搭上自己的生命
The kind of people who risk their lives
只为了我们夜晚能够安心地走在大街小巷的人
so that we can walk safe at night in our own neighborhoods.
也就是我们这位地检大人
The ones our esteemed District Attorney
拼命想要打压的人
here is trying so hard to destroy.
纽约需要这些人
New York needs these people.
我们需要...英雄
We need... heroes.
肃静
Order.
他们提供的帮助
The help they offer...
和他们提供的希望
and the hope that they provide.
弗兰克·卡塞尔想帮忙  但他做过了头
Frank Castle wanted to help, but he took it too far.
他朝人开枪  他杀人
He shot people, he killed people.
这违反了法律
It's against the law.
他一次又一次地违反了法律
And he broke that law many, many times.
我跟你们一样不喜欢他
Now, I don't like him any more than you do,
但是  他不是一名普通的罪犯
but here's the thing, he's not a common criminal.
他的本意不坏
He's not malicious in intent.
弗兰克·卡塞尔其实是个好人  他只是...
Frank Castle is actually a good man. He just...
他现在不知道对与错的区别
He doesn't know the difference between right and wrong anymore.
他不该为此受到惩罚
And he doesn't need punishment for that.
他应该得到帮助
He needs help.
我们的帮助
Our help.
这位弗兰克·卡塞尔就是这样的人
That's the kind of man Frank Castle is.
现在该由你们来决定做怎样的陪审团了
And now, you have to decide what kind of jury you want to be.
我没有问题了  法官大人
No further questions, Your Honor.
法...
Your, uh...
法官大人
Your Honor?
我能说些什么吗
Can I say something?
可以
You may.
那些...
You know those, uh...
那些人
Those people?
那些我击毙的人  我杀死的人
The ones I put down, the people I killed?
如果重来  我还会再杀一次
I want you to know that I'd do it all again.
这就是一场马戏表演
This is a circus, all right?
是场戏  是场演出
It's a charade, it's an act.
-说什么我疯了都是狗屁  -注意措辞
- It's bullshit about how crazy I am. - Language.
我没有疯
I ain't crazy!
I'm not crazy.
好吗
Okay?
我知道我做了什么
I know what I did.
我知道我是谁
I know who I am.
我不需要你们的帮助
And I do not need your help.
我做的就是我脑子里想的事
I'm smack-dab in the middle of my right goddamn mind,
那些混球...
and any scumbag, any...
那些渣滓  那些蝼蚁
any lowlife, any maggot
那些被我干掉的混蛋  我杀了他们...
piece of shit that I put down, I did it...
-是因为我喜欢这么做  -肃静
- because I liked it! - Order!
我爱这样做  我坐在这  我...我渴望
Hell, I loved it! I'm sittin' here, I'm... I'm just itching.
我渴望再来一次
I'm itching to do it again.
你以为呢...
And you think... What,
你以为能送我去什么疯人院吗
you think you're gonna send me to a nuthouse?
找什么医生就能
Some doctor, they're gonna
阻止我做我想做的事吗
get me to stop from doing what I want to do?
不可能的事  想都别想
Well, that ain't happening! Not on my watch!
你们都叫我惩罚者  对吧
You people, you call me the Punisher, ain't that right?
大坏蛋惩罚者
The big bad Punisher.
-法警  -我在这儿
- Bailiff. - Well, here I am!
-带证人出去  -你想要就来啊
- Remove the witness. - You want it, you got it!
我是惩罚者  我就在这
I am the Punisher! I'm right here!
你想要就来试试啊
You want it, I'll give it to you.
今天你们过来想听我哀嚎哭求
And anybody who came here today to hear me whine, to hear me beg?
做梦去吧
Well, you can kiss my ass!
听到了吗  我有罪
Do you hear me? I'm guilty.
来吧  法官  我有罪  听到了吗
Come on, please, Judge! I'm guilty, you hear me?
我有罪  我有罪
I'm guilty! I'm guilty!
我要把他们都杀了  我要杀了每一个人
I'll kill every one of 'em! I'll kill every single one!
怎么会发生这种事
How the hell did this happen?
我昨天跟弗兰克见面时他不是这样的
That wasn't the Frank I met with yesterday.
伙计们
Guys...
-我觉得有人抓住了他的把柄  -让他干什么
- I think somebody got to him. - Convincing him of what?
大喊着要求被判终生监禁吗
Yelling his way to multiple life sentences?
-你激怒了他  -什么  我没有...
- You provoked him. - What? I didn't...
-你在说什么...  -我都跟你说清楚了
- What are you talking-- - I had it lined up for you.
我们本来能做到的
We could have done this.
我们可以减轻判罚
We could have gotten the charges reduced.
你只要让弗兰克开口讲他的故事
All you had to do was get Frank to tell his story.
-福吉  他不合作  -你却扯到
- Foggy, he wasn't cooperating! - Instead you veer off
什么义警的头上
into vigilante-land!
很高兴我们输了
I'm glad we lost.
你听到了吗  我很高兴
You hear me? I'm glad.
-福吉...  -凯伦  别管他
- Foggy... - Karen, let him go.
我不想听
I don't want to hear it.
-凯伦  我能跟你谈谈吗  -我不想
- Karen, can I talk to you for five seconds, please? - I don't want to
再听什么狗屁借口了
hear another bullshit excuse!
也许你酗酒  也许你参加搏击俱乐部
Maybe you are an alcoholic. Maybe you're in a fight club.
也许你跟一群女人上床
Maybe you are sleeping with a whole harem of women.
我都不在乎  我受够了
I don't care, I'm done.
你说得没错
You're right.
这座城市的确需要英雄
This city really needs heroes.
但你不是其中之一
But you're not one of them.
你肯定感觉糟透了
You gotta feel like shit.
回床上去
Go back to bed.
我连站都站不稳
I can barely stand.
那就回到床上去
Then go back to bed.
不
No.
我不想再和你一起了
I don't want to be with you anymore.
我想和他一起
I want to be with him.
-别傻了  -他需要更多训练
- Don't be stupid. - He needs more training.
他第一次接触手和会
The Hand is new to him--
软弱
Soft.
马特·默多克很软弱
Matt Murdock is soft.
他让你变软弱
He made you soft.
你放下了你的防备
You let your guard down.
回床上去吧  艾丽
Go back to bed, Ellie.
-我不是小孩  -你不能和他一起
- I'm not a child. - You can't be with him.
为什么
Why?
你无法改变你的本性
You can't change what you are.
马修认为我可以
Matthew thinks I can.
我相信他
And I believe him.
出去...
Get out...
趁我还没失去耐心
before I get nasty.
你在威胁我吗
Are you threatening me?
你说得没错
You're damn right, I am.
快滚
Go.
你觉得在他发现...
What do you think he'll say...
你到底是谁...
when he finds out...
你一直是怎样的人后
what you are?
他会说什么
What you've always been?
你还没有告诉他
Haven't told him yet...
对吗
have ya?
出去
Get out.
除了救你以外...
Aside from saving your ass...
你根本不知道
you have no idea
我保护你躲过了怎样的劫难
what I've protected you from.
我能保护我自己
I can protect myself.
走着瞧吧
We'll find out.
别管这些业余的了  该把大家集结起来了
Enough with these amateurs. Time to get the band back together.
去高墙
Head to the Wall.
棍叟在哪儿
Where's Stick?
我做出了选择
I made my choice.
他不喜欢
He didn't like it.
我想跟你一起
I want to be with you.
这世界上只有你相信我是好人
The only person in this world who believes I'm good.
你今天输了
You lost today.
没关系
It doesn't matter.
你不仅仅输了一个案子
You lost more than just the case.
是啊
Yeah.
但我没有输掉你
I didn't lose you.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不抱歉
I'm not.
要怎么办呢
How does this work?
我们俩
You and me?
我们要怎么在一起呢
How can we make it work?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是我们会想出办法的
But we're gonna figure it out.
但不是现在
Not now, though.
现在你需要休息
Right now, you need to rest.
你为谁效命
Who do you work for? Huh?
谁派你来的
Who sent you?
回答我
Answer me! Huh?
你告诉他们  不管他们是谁
You tell them, whoever they are,
我都会找到他们  到时候  我会...
I'm gonna find them, and when I do, I'm gonna--
不...
No...
你...你只是个孩子
You're... You're just a kid.
艾丽卡  不...不
Elektra, no... No...
你做了什么
What did you do?
我就是这样的人
This is who I am.
你还想要我吗
Do you still want me?
马修
Matthew.
Matthew!
你没事的  你没事的
You're okay... You're okay...
这个交给我
I got this one.
谁下的命令
On whose orders?
典狱长的  你有什么意见吗
The warden's. You got a problem with that?
没人跟我们说过
No one tells us anything down here.
看着我  弗兰克  看着我
Hey, look at me, Frank! Look at me!
我要捅死你
I'm gonna stick you!
我保证
That's a promise!
我向你保证
I promise you!
就在这里
Right through here.
看来你收到我的讯息了
I see you got my message.